And
welcome to the
sale,
we probably should have started with us, Zina,
then finished with the electric car, I
was afraid of Jiayu, suppressing, hacking to the river,
Lama, dragged a kilo, we,
Lama, sound against the river, teacher, guru, and
this tragedy that it’s hard to hear for a
very long time, that now the words up the mountain
have received some kind of bad meaning, and
we said the
laziest, you can’t explain the fault, cliff, I didn’t hear,
I don’t hear less
[music],
so
I don’t know why I can’t hear at Keshi, I can’t
hear you well, what
in the city there are somewhere around 10,000 people and
we were driving,
people are clearly something rumors about the amount and
[music],
so very harmonic lines, it is seen where it
goes first.  I can't hear well, I ask, I ask, I
still can't hear a word
[music]
did they merge
because I was in Nepal and I
came to Bangalore and they said that it was their
center of dharma, it was like
they brought from there to there, we
mix our dharma in houses, that is, in
their families, a lama layman, I'll give you
the names now and it's me who's not very good at these
lines,
fly
in later, remember,
he taught you, according to that, a
heart student, the main J
in this line, it's important to at least know
the lines of
teachers who
taught this and this, everyone needs to
go through the input, there are 1000 pages of us and we
know who taught which page,
it was never spoiled, never
said
yes, I'll think of something here in the hotel, no
such thing, everything is documented, you
know who taught whose
USA is an abbreviation for
you, the NBA Torji grids, that's where the
other solution of other
vision means
diamond years and he described the
famous
8th verse of the development of a kind
heart, probably the very famous one
80-ti closet
kindergarten or had to delete your
beautiful
opening verses
ball except for
the miracles of BSMP k-pop Dan Sharova creator of the
Seibu festival case ball 2 this is
his
check we will wet the whole he was the first Saul Jong in
seven parts of
Chimera Sochi we have the first who recorded it
he made it open he began to openly
teach it
during the Chicago era and
it became open studies became
open this is what we are now studying with you
and it's funny because they don't
say that it began either during the
Chicago era and
it began when it was lost
appeared on this planet friends don't
say at the time they speak very beautifully
very respectfully speaking in their heads
the following apparently an
open book and
could even 100 there is such a thing
when a book is like an open book we can
now study the teachings are open and
I so the third doctrine
we point out the picture was
hybrid gasoline and then it became electrified and this
open teaching and
we are lucky that it is very open
so in 1150 it became open
teachings and we are lucky
by the way
if you know well but we have reached
Sandakov's place  This is such a stylistic
direct technique, find a standard one, I know
more than a tooth, and
let me tell you a little story about the
people who are related to our
not programs and
[music]
we will talk about greatness and the creators
now
we are somewhere in the middle of an hour and during this
exercise is called
[music]
people are great great rockers as we
say yes it is called STD what
stylistic we are now now
in such a place Alan Gripa in
such a section during which we
talk about what kind of work all
these people have done and
yes we will talk about those people in
Tirana takes and who taught this
practice and first recorded that is why
you see different versions of this silk mode
and we were very lucky
that one of the first books
that was printed Tibetan
printed
means
such metal
letters that were directly secured with letters
and
we remember that in Tibetan it consists of several
parts and we say, for example, one letter
and
imagine how these parts are
screwed into a sheet, for example, Jung
I, so these are letters and
imagine that you need to manually
each of these parts of the lips KFK in order to
then compose the complete  picture and then you
attach it and then you
print and they will destroy it again, take it off again
or force it again, this all happened before
computers before books started
printing, as far as I remember,
this
region was invented by the
Dalai Lama, the teacher of the Dalai Lama,
he collected books, he was a collector of
sin, like our guy, he was quick with 100 dollars,
who is the oldest
collector, didn't have time to give, he simply
answered, arena, people give,
he found,
found
in southern India, the religion of Nagarjuna,
500 years ago, went there, why are we talking about this
here now,
I'm a flu
collector, cleric
[music], he was crazy
about books, and this was his
passion
after he walked and
Igor Incarna appeared with a young
man for 12,
by the way, I lived with them and he allowed me
to see this library, I saw a
lot of rich books,
he was the first person who collected
all his jongs together and connected them
together, this is, of course, a very huge
achievement,
all the important ones on jongs, I, after 1000 years, he
collected  They didn't make one
collection,
and
we made them open, they are
online. Can you imagine
16,000 or 16,000 pages of
jong, and they are free, you can
see them, you can print them. Here
we have what's happening
next, and
now he tells us a little about the life of the
intestines. He was without steps. Keep
holding what this means. Yes,
he was spiritually working, but he was not
initiated. He did
not have this degree, and then even
earlier, he did not have the degree of Kesha. They simply
said that in the spiritual teacher,
Belyashi news appeared much more about
likes smi2,
this is one of the most ancient Tibetan
traditions, and so he was born Ningbo.
The service for Jin has not existed for a hundred years, and
Gelug
nigma means original authentic, the
earliest Buddhists, they were called nigma, it is called the
oldest and most ancient.
He was born in a family on a PDA.
He was born in a family,
his people
were engaged in studying the practice of the goddess, the
secret practice. He
was born in this family,
these are people who secretly practiced the
highest teaching, and
he
studied the 5 great sciences, this is
classical poetry,
astrology, those.  taxes and which were studied
then by Wendy and Buddhism
logic
grammar medicine and
there are niches and art for example lower
subjects are sculpture architecture
drawing and so on he will strengthen and
master
or he wanted this money for him little
knew more about
him the text diamond relief caught his eye
every time when there is when there is a benefit in
any situation if it is a profitable
situation Adam-Adam this to another
every time there
is some kind of
loss I will take it upon myself and
this is a very beautiful practice you can
use it throughout the day you
can also use it at work in
business every time there is some kind of risk
you take them upon yourself and every time there is
some benefit and you see a big
profit
you give and I want want to want to keep
it you conduct a debate and give
and
this is very beautiful and the attitude
to how we treat losses and
profits because they received
losing my wife is not here yet and
because she cares for a cancer patient
recently lost a large piece of her
business because she
cared for a
cancer patient you give  You give what
you earn, you give and you do it
quietly, you take on the expenses, you take on the
pain,
so he became one of the smallest
teachers of Buddhism and
he fell in love with these ideas and he
already says how beautiful it is, he is already a
blogger,
but he saw this Jones and said this is
beautiful, this beauty,
he saw this lodging in
8 verses, call him to the infirmary,
I began research,
tried, began to apply these in
practice, began to practice and here is a very
interesting here is a very funny story
I read it a long time ago and
it is in the book there is a story of these
eight verses
[music]
somewhere for which on the way I had the same
times, of course, there were no hotels and he
just stopped at someone's to
spend the night,
knocked on the door, they said, I travel,
never, of course, come in, here's dinner, here's my
wife's, here's your
bed and of course no one took money for this
when there were no hotels, of course, and it was the
right of the traveler to knock
on the door and it was the responsibility of the people
who lived there to offer food and a
bed, by the way, is also very beautiful and
she somehow he stayed with someone  There
was another traveler in the house and
next to him in the next room and this
traveler quoted the
arson of a diamond algo
he quoted eating such a zone
began to listen carefully
to the yard wow
this became
ion met this guy looking
where you learned him said I
taught this tour garlic myself from you without he
taught me this could have I
said great I want too I also want to
learn how how can you meet this
where I have already seen myself I will find him I also
want he can teach me this
told him how to get to how to find
his fairies and here are the details of his line and he
went found him and this
diamond lion he was no longer alive and a
very famous moment when he
got to him
yes it's time I think to turn on the air conditioner
he got to him he was no longer
alive and
he of course was very upset says and is there really no
one who could teach me
this and
lock the nba means
from the land of llamas
his students were present and they
taught this lojer his students taught the
cheek of this boat the next picture there is
no
practice yes that's it
What's cool here is that the students
were so
devoted,
so attentive, and
wrote everything down carefully, and they learned the
dharma so well that they perfectly
conveyed it, and a boat of tricks, you
know what I'm talking about, this is such a
great example,
this is
such a classic example in Buddhism, and
when the second generation, when the generation
managed to convey it, it's clear, very ordinary,
they wrote it down, they wrote it down, they
worked very hard, and they maintained this
line, this is a very famous example of how
they practically corrected this, which,
for example, the first generation didn't do, they
understood what I was asking for, they studied it,
practiced it so well that
[music] it's
already passed on to the third
generation, this girl, we have a different
generation, the picture means grandmother,
grandfather on the left, mother and child, the third
generation, I really like this, I'm
happy about this story, in fact,
imagine, he was so upset
because he found this house, and he was
no longer alive, helkat lord, when I
won't learn this, I will never recognize him,
he was surrounded,
like an
atmosphere, such an
environment in a cafe,
he was surrounded from all sides
[music],
they accepted him into the master's house, this was  the
next generation and
they were even better than the environment itself, there was a
whole group, it was already the next
generation who were so devoted and
they supported each other that if the same thing were true
without it being one
teacher and x was he passed it on to
several students, it was the
next generation and they survived they
were successful and that's what the
second generation achieved, they
really, first of all, learned everything,
secondly, they supported the first
generation there was only one teacher and the
second was somewhere around 5-10 students
who were very devoted to their teacher
and then it naturally spread,
this is what
happened in Tibet, it became open and
it just spread, it
reached Arizona further
and
then he returned home and practiced
received bodhichitta, it worked, he
studied it and
he worked and upon returning home he
practiced, most likely, probably
also in a retreat in the
same place as us with the action in
Diamond Mountain and
received bodhichitta, the
next one,
no, another one,
this is by the way the most real thing, what a
person with leprosy looked like after they
came up with a
treatment and that's
how it ate away at your body, it was
very, it's possible  It was easy, it was easily
transmitted, and
famous saints in Christianity, like the
snake, by the way, worked with such
sick people, with the afflicted, and
tried to help them, everyone was afraid, of course, to
touch them, and
he was famous for looking for such
people and caring for them,
he avoided sin, on the contrary, he tried to
find them and cared for Abel Chronah, he
touched her and care was shown, and
he taught them, and
he helped a large number of actions,
problems,
this practice on the steam step will come out, sheng
became
famous as a hare,
what does darma mean for leprosy, and
he became famous as darma from John
for teaching these people,
and
this helped people who were sick, and he
also so forget about himself that they
got rid of their fear, and it
seems to me that Jesus also cared for
such people, and
people stopped calling him like these
step media step
water chong, they began to call him tarmo leper teacher
Chicago,
I thought it's a
pity
that some part still remains a
secret, secret after he
studied, he healed lepers on
It was John's duty to teach them, he said it. Yes, it's a
shame and a disgrace.
We should have a new video. It's a shame and a
disgrace.
It's a promise
that it's all secret and top secret. It
should be open.
Sindu Bambo means it's a shame, a disgrace, it's sad,
sad, and
he was the first to teach it
openly.
He broke tradition and taught it openly,
which is why it's now available to us.
He recorded it for the first time and
created this seven-part structure,
then it became known as such, etc.
from seven parts, a stepping icon,
maybe you want to know what this 70 is,
but
I'm kidding, you have to give in and
I'll tell you briefly what these seven
parts are so that you fill them out.
It seems like I compiled them, I wrote them down. Yes, yes,
I made a list, exactly.
Hurray!
I did it. This
means meadows. It means oral
transmission. That is, it would be good to hear this,
and so it was passed down from generation to
generation, like in a rock and roll song. Even
you heard it from someone and then pass it on to
others. So, let's
see what this diagram of
parts and points is. The first is
preparatory practices. This is when we
take refuge, for example,
preparatory practice. The second is the
practice itself.
How to develop a desire for enlightenment. Almost
read. Take it. It's interesting. This is a separate
section on how to turn problems
back.
By the way, we take this section and teach them to
business people. By the way, you recently completed
the program
[music],
which was attended by almost 110 thousand people.
How to turn problems back. A masterpiece. We just
used this part.
It's great.
4. This is an overview of the
entire practice. If you practice in what way
during your life, what kind of
person will you become?
You will become a person after such
practice.
signs that you have achieved this when you
can say that I did this, I
achieved this. This helps a lot. There
must be some
official definitions. If you
do this, you will get a beating. That is, there are
some signs. Signs that you have achieved
this and you take responsibility.
You say, everything is here. I make a
promise. Turn me off, I will
study this. And 7. I
started in Tibetan.
This is what the teacher teaches you. The secret is that you
serve the teacher. At some point, I
had the same thing. If I were worthy of the honor of
serving my teacher for 25 years, my teachers
said that he uses it. I told him to
give it. On the contrary, I
use it. It
allows me to be positive. He allows me not to have
dishes with me. I wash the dishes after him. Don't
worry, I
get enough. It
sounds like maybe my friends said
less. Oh yes, he uses that where there are no
guys, it's me. The impulse is because he
allows me to serve them and
I am a very, very
happy person.
I believe that I am blessed by
this. Don't talk nonsense. I use it. He doesn't
allow me to wash the dishes from allowing me not to
build a house for him and this makes me
very, very happy and  He got me
successful no matter how
I started
here, giving away money, and so these are such
advice, seven parts, there
are some things, and which
person teaches, gives an tai na,
one of my teachers, and he says here,
your Tibetan is
getting better and better, but you're
still jealous of me,
this is called when you are alone with your
teacher, he says such very personal
things, and I said I need to work on it, I enjoyed the
recording, I don't need to please yet, the
YouTube video, and I'm like, how is it that you
work well because of what you
advise, it's great,
he says, for now, give it away, study the description,
and then you spend it with envy, she wove a
motive and domain, this means that what to
talk about alone,
personally, intimately, in a conversation, I, this is very cool,
this is great,
you can't do this if you don't have a
lama,
by the way,
sometimes this is in
the words of the legs,
sometimes before the book was called the
essence of nectar, and there is another lama rim,
which is called the essence of nectar,
next to the
Mongolian teachings, we are not talking
about this here, these are two jong, it was also called
one of the essence  Hectares
and why was it called that? 100 dollars of
the word nectar, what does it mean? So,
someone
from glasses, it's easy.
I need a definition. Nobody up to
100 dollars
can buy more trees.
Yes, it means in Greek
and
Sanskrit, which means
traveling there further. Dara is a lady
who
nectar is
traveling further beyond.
Not Amrita. That's
wrong to pronounce it that way. There's no
such thing as Ray, and we're not Amrita.
I don't know. The
vowels are wrong. In
general, it
sounds terrible.
Repeat. Amrita is an exact translation of
nectar and very kind.  What does
[music] mean,
nectar of immortality,
but he says here, and
here's the next picture, a
peach tree, a cafe, a peach tree, I
don't
know why, stand, let's call it something else,
they call it
peach juice, a normal year, peach
nectar, but it's strange, it's
often written on the package that it's
peach nectar, it's unclear why it's not
juice, and
this should remind you that there is an
alternative name for this,
in Jonga, the
essence of Victor, which means by death,
was very much in Tibetan, in Sanskrit, it's
something like
possessing, when I was there, and
why was it called that?
Because if you study this, la joc, the
muscles achieve vigor, the
whole world complains about this
sweet nectar, taste this sweet,
sometimes
I personally think
[music]
call the
stepper La Joc somehow, well, how terrible, in fact, maybe you should
really call it by its old
name, the essence of Victor,
that is, immortality, great,
Joe, you tried when you were little to come up with a
name, then your
rock band
[music], then maybe it
seems cool to call the name of the
group's hands,
we had so many,
I was there  10,000 houses, what do you call them? Yes, no one does.
We tried it. Start your own
group, no matter what they
call it.
We had white shorts and a green T-
shirt.
Gremlins.
Next time, you'll get money. So
remember,
our first concert was near the pool.
You had a party. We were already nervous and
I even threw up. I think Jill has the
same story.
So, we finished with you for his daddy
when we talked about the greatness of those people
who are connected with Vitaly's transmissions. The
next thing we will consider with you is that
we will sell
you the most replacements.
Bye, and what should we repeat? Elsa Bobo.
What is
the greatness of the teacher and who transmitted
these teachings to us? Now we will do the
teachings ourselves. This is a different subject.
If you know it, to see this
difference, and so a little bit, why is it
already a
diamond? It
seems to me that in Chinese the
same thing has a technical name and there is also
such a popular name.
They seem to me to be different.
You don't say "puppy" Jin Cohen now somehow
differently.
Sancho the sun
in Tibetan, by the way, is the same thing. Chekan is an
old tour, but this is a state of words, and
modern  top scales and
here is exactly what was written by the old
new head and daughter, the
modern word for
diamonds in the
CIS days and in Chinese,
Sochi, I apologize for the Chinese, this is a
dart, it's very cool, and the greatness of this
teaching is that they are like a diamond,
we are all students of the
diamond chart here, and we always immediately
say
that the most durable, the hardest
substance on earth, even if we
break it in this part, yes, each one will be a
diamond,
and
he says
that a good diamond, I apologize,
I have an allergy, a
good diamond has started, it just sparkles
unusually, it seems to me, I tried to
find this picture to depict
this radiance, sparkle, a good
diamond, a real diamond
is like a spark, and even a small spark is
much more powerful than a team, if you
think about it,
but where there is this spark, it retreats, this is
exactly the idea, where there is a spark, a
second, then this is necessary, so it gets scared and
disappears, and the
spark is this light, it conquers, that
is, this piece, a fragment of a
diamond, it is like
sunlight, and
one such ray of light can destroy
all the darkness, no matter how much  It does
n't matter
if you see the stars, this one spark
can destroy a
small ray of light, it destroys and
destroys completely the darkness and at least
somehow retreats and it's
dark here, yes, it cares, it's like
darkness
2, this tendency
to care is number one, this is an
English idiom,
we talk about when we first serve
ourselves, days, this means this
disease, selfishness, when we care about
ourselves,
you can take this, but here are the croissants,
please leave the sour one,
also Jane, this is what CJ writes about,
this is the tendency to first take care of
yourself, there
was such a book
in Mike, wouldn't it be
Steller, what and where said
that in principle it's great when you
first care only about yourself,
this book disappeared, guess why it
didn't help anyone, apparently, and
these teachings
that we will study with you, this
spark is a ray of light
that can develop this
habit when we
first care only about ourselves will allow us to
get rid of this habit
when we only think about ourselves
selfishly,
when Dracula is encountered, when a
cross or the Bible is pointed at Dracula
and he gets scared, this is approximately  so
and
gas 31
and he
accept this idea about the
show yes
there is such a plant
that can cure
any
immortelle
this is such a plant can cure the pharmacopoeia
thank you yes and it
can it's like nitroglycerin helps
with heart disease can
immediately help help you cure and
pharma copy pharmacopoeia
this is nitroglycerin
and helps
cure heart disease and
these teachings are like a spark of light a ray of
light in the family it's exactly like this
debit Oles
heals helps with heart disease
but people should take it in my opinion throughout their
lives
well then there is some kind of ad
he is trying to stop me
we were in San Diego
we lived there
my my father and my mother lived there and
she had dust and had a
captain's license she
and he I apologize
deserved it
he said that he could sell boats
better than my mother
this was not a captain
and and it took there were
such
when they push the boat and you
need a lot of some distance
somewhere about 5 mi for it to
slow down it is very high somewhere the
size of a ten-story building
an aircraft carrier
We got very close to her, such a terrible sound,
why am I telling you this, I'll
see you in 10 minutes, I'm still here, it's
that
propeller, it's huge, it
could just be the size of this studio, everything in this
room,
in any case, and that's it, a
break